Taking stock of the year, coaching,
remobilizing the troops, and defining the
objectives for the current year
were the key issues at this latest
edition of Prudential
Beneficial Insurance's kickoff meeting. This
strategic meeting between top management and
sales agents took place in
Douala over two days, from January 12th to
13th, 2024. The meeting was marked
by the presence of Prudential
Beneficial Insurance CEO Eddie Fort Brown. The
kickoff revealed itself
through discussions on
team development. It was also a major opportunity to
examine
the institution's progress, a
considerable increase in sales over the last few years,
praised by the
CEO. This progress
contributes to the
organization's development by focusing on
improving customer service. If
you have an
advantage, time,
resources, or knowledge, you must share it.
We're talking about customer service and customer
satisfaction. During
several working sessions,
top management focused on
integrating the new directions and
major challenges of the new year.
[Music]
and
the CEO reiterated it in
[Music]
his kickoff, which ended with a
gala evening and an
awards ceremony for the best agents who distinguished themselves through
their dedication and
commitment. Benur Entreise is committed to
contributing to a better quality of
life for citizens and strives
daily to offer better
services and products to its valued
customers. Benurent insurance
for every life, for every
future.